<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Owa</string>
    <string name="naira">&#8358;</string>
    <string name="cancellation_policy">Free cancellation policy for 24 hours. If you wan\'t to cancel after 24 hours, you will only get
        a 50% refund.</string>
    <string name="bullet">•</string>
    <string name="agreement">You agree to rent this dwelling on a month-to-month basis, payable in advance on each month calendar year.
 \n\n
The security/cleaning deposit on this dwelling has been included in the total charges.

\n\nTENANTS AGREE TO THE FOLLOWING:  \n\n
\n1) to accept the dwelling "as is," having already inspected it.
\n2) to keep yards and garbage areas clean.
\n3) to keep from making loud noises and disturbances and to
play music and broadcast  programs at all times so as not to disturb other people\'s peace and quiet.
\n4) not to paint the dwelling without first getting Owner(s) written permission.
\n5) to park motor vehicles in the assigned space and to keep that space clean of oil drippings and grease.
\n6) not to repair motor vehicle on the premises (unless it is in an enclosed garage) if such repairs will take
longer than a day.
\n7) to allow Owner(s) to inspect the dwelling, work on it, or show it to prospective tenants at any and all reasonable times.
\n8) not to keep any liquid-filled furniture in this
dwelling.
\n9)  to pay rent by check or money order made out to the Owner(s)
\n10) to pay for repairs of all damage, they or their guests have caused.
\n11) to pay for any windows broken in the dwelling while they live there.

\n\nViolation of any part of this Agreement or nonpayment of rent when due shall be cause for eviction under applicable code sections.  The prevailing party (shall/shall not) recover reasonable legal service fees involved.

\n\nTenants hereby acknowledge that they have read this Agreement, understand it, agree to it.</string>
    <string name="lockdown_policy">Please note that we would charge you one month ahead. This ensures that we both have enough time to make decisions on our tenants staying or moving out.</string>
    <string name="answer1">Owa is a platform where you get apartments you can move into quickly and without hassles.</string>
    <string name="answer2">It takes an average of 4 days to get your apartment all setup for you to move in</string>
    <string name="answer3">We have a lockdown policy that allows us decide if you should stay or we should find a budget friendly apartment for you</string>
    <string name="answer4">Yes, payment of apartment is automated, you can as well fund your wallet and pay up</string>


    <string-array name="months">
        <item>Set Months</item>
        <item>1 Month</item>
        <item>2 Months</item>
        <item>3 Month</item>
        <item>4 Months</item>
        <item>5 Month</item>
        <item>6 Months</item>
        <item>7 Month</item>
        <item>8 Months</item>
        <item>9 Month</item>
        <item>10 Months</item>
        <item>12 Month</item>
        <item>12 Months</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="one_guest">
        <item>Set Guest</item>
        <item>1 Guest</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="two_guests">
        <item>Set Guest</item>
        <item>1 Guest</item>
        <item>2 Guests</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="three_guests">
        <item>Set Guest</item>
        <item>1 Guest</item>
        <item>2 Guests</item>
        <item>3 Guests</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="four_guests">
        <item>Set Guest</item>
        <item>1 Guest</item>
        <item>2 Guests</item>
        <item>3 Guests</item>
        <item>4 Guests</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="five_guests">
        <item>Set Guest</item>
        <item>1 Guest</item>
        <item>2 Guests</item>
        <item>3 Guests</item>
        <item>4 Guests</item>
        <item>5 Guests</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="six_guests">
        <item>Set Guest</item>
        <item>1 Guest</item>
        <item>2 Guests</item>
        <item>3 Guests</item>
        <item>4 Guests</item>
        <item>5 Guests</item>
        <item>6 Guests</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="property_type">
        <item>Entire Apartment</item>
        <item>Room</item>
        <item>Bed Space</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>Gender</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="option">
        <item>No</item>
        <item>Yes</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
